[phone vibrating]
[Sung Jinwoo groaning]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Hello?
[SUNG JINAH]
Jinwoo!
You weren't still asleep,
were you?
[SUNG JINWOO] Yeah,
I was a little worn out.
[SUNG JINAH]
Do you realize what time it is?
Wakey-wakey!
You're supposed to meet
with my teacher today!
[Sung Jinwoo gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[SUNG JINAH]
Uhh.
Are you my brother?
'Cause you look...
What? Bad?
[GO GUNHEE]
It's been over ten years
since gates began appearing.
Through these gates
are dungeons
inhabited by magic beasts,
and the battles between
these beasts and the humans
who've awakened
the abilities to fight them
only continue to intensify.
♪
To pay his sick mother's bills
and little sister's tuition,
Jinwoo Sung took up work
as a hunter,
despite being the lowest
possible level, E-rank.
In most cases, a hunter's
powers and rank remain the same
from the moment
of their awakening.
♪
However, in the aftermath
of a horrific raid
on a double dungeon,
Jinwoo gained
the ability to level up,
as though in a video game.
As he grew stronger in battle,
he obtained the recipe
for the Elixir of Life,
said to be able
to cure any disease,
as well as a new job class,
allowing him to command
an army of shadows,
the shadow monarch.
[SUNG JINAH] I...wouldn't say
you look bad, but...
It's for a meeting, though,
I can't wear a tracksuit.
[chuckles]
You're living proof
people can always change.
[whimpering]
Wow.
Like, who is he?
Well, look at you,
Mister Popular.
[SUNG JINAH] You going on
a hot date later or something?
[sighs]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Shut up.
[SUNG JINAH] Ow-ow-ow-ow,
ow! Ah-ow! Ow-ow!
[FEMALE TEACHER 13A]
Jinah's wonderful.
Her behavior is exemplary,
as are her grades.
And she's a role model
to the other students,
which we teachers
always appreciate.
Glad to hear.
[FEMALE TEACHER 13A] She's
excelled on her mock exams,
so she'll certainly qualify
for the med school
she's aiming for.
Just refrain from
adding more pressure.
-[yawns]
-[SUNG JINWOO] Yes, ma'am.
That was everything
I needed to go over,
but um, do you have time
for something less official?
Sure.
What is it?
Just curious, but what if
Jinah were to awaken?
Would you let her
become a hunter
and give up her current path?
[Sung Jinwoo gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
No.
Good.
That's what
I thought you'd say.
So then...
Mister Sung, I realize this
may be asking a lot of you,
but please.
[door opens]
[footfall]
Mm?
[HAN SONG-YI]
Aah?
[gasps]
[sighs]
Did I miss something?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Huh.
Do you know this girl?
[HAN SONG-YI]
Wait.
Are you...Jinah's brother?
It's a small world, isn't it?
[sighs]
Look, I dunno what our
teacher told you about me,
but I'm done with school,
and I refuse
to give up on hunting.
[SUNG JINWOO]
You're an E-rank.
You can't earn
a living like that.
Our strike team let you
make some easy money,
but that's not the norm.
[HAN SONG-YI] If you're
only here to lecture me,
you can go home now.
Besides, you're E-rank,
too, Mister!
[sighs]
I'm not trying
to make you quit.
Huh?!
Come on.
[airplane engine whirring]
Hello, Hunter Hwang.
[WOO JINCHUL]
Welcome home.
♪
Like I'd call this
outdated dump home.
But being met fresh
off the plane
by the chief manager
of the Hunter's Association
is an unexpected treat.
Do you intend
to stay very long?
[scoffs]
I don't have enough love for
this country to stick around.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
You can unclench.
You didn't come all the way
back to the homeland
you abandoned
just for the chance
to find those two hunters?
[HWANG DONGSOO]
"Find" them?
You know that's not
the right word.
I suggest you Surveillance Team
folks play dumb.
When it happens,
it'll be inside a dungeon.
First the E-rank,
then the D-rank.
Or are you stupid enough
to try and stop me?
If you want, go for it,
I could use a laugh.
I do what my job requires,
let's just leave it at that.
[airplane engine whirring]
[Hwang Dongsoo scoffs]
♪
[GO GUNHEE]
So, they had wings.
The real issue at hand
is the bodies fell into the sea
and we didn't recover them.
But you are saying
these giant ants
are capable of flight?
Only over shorter stretches
for now, but given time?
Hmm.
We'll have to look into it.
I'll make the arrangements.
Hm.
[SUNG JINWOO] Manager Ahn.
Mister Hyun.
Good to see you.
[AHN SANGMIN]
It's been a while!
I'll admit, I wasn't expecting
to hear from you.
[chuckles]
What a pleasant surprise!
-[HAN SONG-YI] Hello.
-[both gasping]
[AHN SANGMIN]
Oh!
You're that girl
from the other day!
She's with me,
I'm sorry to impose.
No, if you're the one asking,
then it's never imposing,
Hunter Sung.
[HYUN KICHUL] Yeah,
now I see why you wanted
to sit in on some training.
-[HYUN KICHUL] It's for her.
-[SUNG JINWOO] It is.
[AHN SANGMIN] Well,
your timing couldn't be better.
This area's designated
as a high-frequency gate zone,
and as luck would have it,
a C-rank one opened up
just this morning.
[KIM CHUL] Shut your
mouths and let's move.
We're not here on a field trip.
Right, we're almost finished.
Who's that guy?
[AHN SANGMIN]
A-rank Hunter Chul Kim.
And as you can see,
he's a tank.
[SUNG JINWOO]
A-rank, huh?
He's new.
Higher rank aside,
a rookie is still a rookie
and we train ours up.
And because every team
needs a leader,
Chul Kim was picked
for this one.
We let him know
you'd be tagging along.
-Been in a crap mood
ever since. -!
What are they thinking?
Forcing me to babysit
a couple of E-ranks.
Unbelievable.
So, apart from our
A-rank leader,
the rest of the strike team
will consist of five B-ranks
and two C's, which makes
eight hunters in total.
[AHN SANGMIN] The addition
of you two brings the count up
to a nice, safe ten.
[SUNG JINWOO] I was hoping
she'd change her mind
after she sees
how brutal raids can be.
But...that lineup is stacked.
If it goes too well,
it defeats the purpose.
-[HYUN KICHUL] Hunter Sung?
-Ah?
So, the goal's for our rookies
to learn in there.
Just sit back and watch
if you could, please.
Right, you got it.
[AHN SANGMIN]
Well, let the training begin!
Don't have to tell me twice.
[footfall]
Are we doing this?
For real?
Yep, I'll be right behind you.
Hm.
[footfall]
[crackling]
Ah!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Something's not right,
what is this feeling?
♪
[crackling]
[gasping]
[SUNG JINWOO]
No. No, no, no!
[gasping]
What the heck's going on?
[both gasping]
[HYUN KICHUL]
Hunter Sung?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Manager Ahn!
Contact your primary
strike squad!
Do it now!
[Hyun and Ahn gasping]
[BAEK YOONHO]
A red gate?
How did a C-rank gate turn red?
Never mind,
I'm on my way there!
♪
[wind howling]
[gasps]
♪
[GO MYUNGHWAN]
Where's the gate?
How do we get back?
[MALE B-RANK MEMBER 13A] Will
someone explain what happened?
-It turned red.
-[group gasping]
♪
Is there a big difference
between a red gate
and a normal one?
They're more dangerous by far.
Once you step through one,
you'll be completely isolated
from the outside world.
[SUNG JINWOO] You're trapped
until the boss is defeated
or there's a dungeon break,
and no one can send you help.
[HAN SONG-YI]
Trapped?
[SUNG JINWOO] Uh-huh,
and the magic beasts
are usually stronger, too.
[gasps]
[HAN SONG-YI]
But this dungeon is C-rank.
[thuds]
♪
[male B-rank member
13D screaming]
[KIM CHUL]
Stay alert! It's an ambush!
[gasps]
♪
[HAN SONG-YI]
Uh, thank you.
-[SUNG JINWOO] Sure, you okay?
-[HAN SONG-YI] Mm-hm.
Ah!
♪
[KIM CHUL]
Ice elves!
[GO MYUNGHWAN]
Ah, they're so high up!
[sighs]
[SUNG JINWOO] Where most
people wouldn't notice them.
They intentionally
targeted our weakest links.
Which would've included me
two months ago.
♪
[ice shattering]
[exhales]
-[HAN SONG-YI] Mister?
-Ah!
[HAN SONG-YI]
What are ice elves?
[SUNG JINWOO]
A problem.
These elves aren't like
the ones in fairy tales,
they're much more cruel.
Hunters call them Ice Slayers.
[gasps]
All right, listen up!
[KIM CHUL]
As you know, a red gate means
we're cut off from support,
facing B-rank beasts and above.
If you want to live,
I presume you'll obey me,
the highest-ranked
hunter among us.
[group gasping]
With that said,
even I can't command
all of you by myself.
We'll form two groups.
Mine will press on
to clear the gate.
[SUNG JINWOO]
What?
[KIM CHUL] It's our
best chance of survival!
Stand around and debate
if you're fine
with freezing to death
or getting slaughtered!
But I guarantee anyone
who follows me
will make it out alive!
-Sir, I'll join you.
-So will I!
Yeah, me, to--
[grunting]
You stay behind.
Same goes for the observers,
the both of you.
The lower ranks
will only slow us down.
One day in a red gate
equals an hour outside.
Whether we end up
defeating the boss
or waiting for a dungeon break,
we'll be here a while,
maybe even months.
[KIM CHUL]
Caring for deadweight's
-a waste of time and energy.
-[both gasp]
[Sung Jinwoo sighs]
Don't look so depressed,
you guys.
Survive till we clear this
and we'll all go home.
-[PARK HEEJIN] Excuse me.
-[gasping]
Any objections
to me joining the B team?
♪
[KIM CHUL]
Suit yourself.
[footfall]
[KIM CHUL]
Does she pity them?
[scoffs]
What a fool.
♪
Captain Kim didn't notice the
arrows in time, yet you did.
You aren't E-rank, are you?
♪
[PARK HEEJIN] He's an A,
or possibly even an S.
[chuckles]
Nice to meet you.
Um, hi.
[KIM CHUL]
Hey.
We're taking the path that
leads through the clearing.
[SUNG JINWOO]
In that case,
our group will head
for the woods.
Best of luck, then.
♪
[gasping]
Same to you.
Gonna need it.
[wind howling]
Ugh!
Captain?
-To your right.
-[gasping]
[MALE B-RANK MEMBER 13B]
Claw marks.
Made by an ice bear.
The E-rank's little squad
is going to die
faster than I thought.
Ahh, doubt the poor saps have
had any proper training either.
How bad's your luck gotta be
to die while observing a raid?
[KIM CHUL]
Hang on.
They've got a C-rank,
and Heejin Park, who's a B.
Why'd I say "the E-rank's
squad," like he leads them?
[gasps]
[metal clanging]
Let's get ready to fight!
[growling]
♪
[all gasping]
[KIM CHUL] I want all of you
to focus on staying alive.
[roaring]
♪
[thuds]
[roaring]
[Kim Chul growls]
♪
Uh!
[growling]
[Kim Chul growls]
[PARK HEEJIN]
Stop!
[gasping]
[SUNG JINWOO]
What is it?
What's on every tree?
Claw marks.
So, this entire forest
is ice bear territory.
We should turn back
before we cross one.
[both gasp]
I say that we keep
walking down this path.
[PARK HEEJIN]
Why?
If all this is bear territory,
they should be the only threat
we'll need to worry about.
Beats an intelligent enemy
like elves, right?
[gasps]
[PARK HEEJIN]
Since ice bears thrive here,
there must not be a stronger
creature that preys on them.
[sighs]
I hadn't considered that,
but yeah, you're right.
[inhales deeply]
Though, another threat...
would be this damn cold.
[PARK HEEJIN]
Yes.
[crackling]
Here, put these coats on.
Is that summoning magic?
A high-ranked hunter
can barely store
two or three low-level items,
but he pulled out four of 'em
like it's no big deal?
It's warm as toast in here!
[sighs]
[HAN SONG-YI] Okay,
who exactly are you, "mister?"
[footfall]
[sighs]
I'm the reason
you got in this mess,
so it's my job
to keep you safe.
Just don't ask questions.
[sighs]
[groans]
[SUNG JINWOO]
That also applies to you two.
Don't ask me about anything.
No questions, no demands.
[BOTH]
Hmm.
[thuds]
[roaring]
[all gasping]
[growling]
[roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO]
All right...change title.
♪
[crackling]
[BAEK YOONHO] Ah!
It's firmly sealed shut.
Best case scenario
would be Chul Kim
and a handful of B-ranks manage
to make it out of there alive.
♪
The outcome depends
on Hunter Kim's ability
to lead and fight.
[AHN SANGMIN]
Um, sir?
Two others accompanied
our strike team
inside this gate.
[AHN SANGMIN]
One is Jinwoo Sung.
He, uh, caught my eye recently.
What's his rank?
He's E-rank.
H-However, I believe
he had a reawakening!
[BAEK YOONHO] [gasps]
Have you confirmed it?
Well...no.
Not directly, sir.
Hmm.
[engine whirring]
[gasping]
[HWANG DONGSOO]
Would you get a load of this.
It's like a who's who
of White Tiger Guild
bigwigs out here.
That's gotta be an
A-rank gate at least, yeah?
Been a while, Dongsoo.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
It sure has, Yoonho.
Didn't think I'd run into you
on this little business trip.
[BAEK YOONHO]
Why'd you come?
You're supposed
to be in America,
not in our jurisdiction.
[scoffs]
Your "jurisdiction?"
[HWANG DONGSOO]
I got a question for you, then.
If I'm not allowed
on your turf,
the hell is some unaffiliated
E-rank doing on it?
What?
This wuss, Jinwoo Sung.
[BAEK YOONHO]
Hwang wants him, too?
Dragged myself all this way,
and he's inside a red gate.
Didn't even get a look
at the slimy bastard's face.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
And now, he's probably
gonna bite it in there.
♪
[WOO JINCHUL] You're
a lucky man, Jinwoo Sung.
♪
Even the mighty Dongsoo Hwang
can't break through a red gate.
♪
Question is, do you have
enough luck remaining
to escape with your life?
[thuds]
[both gasping]
Well, guess that tracks.
A red gate beast
gives a lot more XP.
So, you are...
what exactly?
[fire crackling]
[HAN SONG-YI] Bear meat's
better than I expected.
[GO MYUNGHWAN]
Can't help but notice
the attacks have dwindled.
Hunter Sung put ice bears
on the endangered species list.
There should still be
some in their dens,
so we can't let
our guards down yet.
But what about that guy?
[HAN SONG-YI] I can't believe
after all that fighting,
he still wants
to work off his meal.
[fire crackling]
[PARK HEEJIN] [sighs]
He's definitely strange.
He sure is.
[wind howling]
[growling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
This should be a fair fight.
Come forth.
♪
It's time
for your first mission.
♪
[roaring]
[growling]
Now go.
♪
[growling]
[roars]
♪
[growls]
[roaring]
♪
[growls]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Powerful attacks.
Infantry regenerates quickly.
I'm quite impressed.
They do drain
a ton of mana, though.
[gasps]
[thuds]
[roaring]
So, you're the leader
of the pack.
♪
[roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO] Wiped out
my shadow soldiers instantly.
And my mana.
♪
You're up, Igris.
[thumping]
[growling]
♪
[roaring]
[sword slashing]
♪
[groaning]
[sword slashing]
Oh, wow.
♪
[growling]
[thuds]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Okay.
If Igris had fought me
with his sword,
I'd definitely
be a dead man.
♪
But my current level
must match his, right?
No, I'm probably still weaker.
♪
Excellent work.
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
Help me!
[growling]
[KIM CHUL]
This isn't real.
I'm set to join the elite
of the White Tigers!
So, it's not real.
It can't be real!
Captain!
[grunts]
-[chuckles]
-Huh!
[screaming]
[wind howling]
♪